(soft music)
♪ Mmm, mmm, mmm, yeah ♪
♪ Some people live for the fortune ♪
♪ Some people live just for the fame ♪
♪ Some people live for the power, yeah ♪
♪ Some people live just to play the game ♪
♪ Some people think ♪
♪ That the physical things ♪
♪ Define what's within ♪
♪ And I've been there before ♪
♪ That life's a bore ♪
♪ So full of the superficial ♪
♪ Some people want it all ♪
♪ But I don't want nothing at all ♪
♪ If it ain't you, baby ♪
♪ If I ain't got you, baby ♪
♪ Some people want diamond rings ♪
♪ Some just want everything ♪
♪ But everything means nothing ♪
♪ If I ain't got you, yeah ♪
♪ Some people search for a fountain ♪
♪ Promises forever young ♪
♪ Some people need three dozen roses ♪
♪ And that's the only way
to prove you love them ♪
♪ Hand me the world ♪
♪ On a silver platter ♪
♪ And what good would it be? ♪
♪ With no one to share ♪
♪ With no one who truly cares for me? ♪
♪ Some people want it all ♪
♪ But I don't want nothing at all ♪
♪ If it ain't you, baby ♪
♪ If I ain't got you, baby ♪
♪ Some people want diamond rings ♪
♪ Some just want everything ♪
♪ But everything means nothing ♪
♪ If I ain't got you, you, you ♪
♪ Some people want it all ♪
♪ But I don't want nothing at all ♪
♪ If it ain't you, baby ♪
♪ If I ain't got you, baby ♪
♪ Some people want diamond rings ♪
♪ Some just want everything ♪
♪ But everything means nothing ♪
♪ If I ain't got you, yeah ♪
(heart beating)
- Yo, let me get coffee thirty
with those big ass feet.